<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-model href="http://www.tei-c.org/release/xml/tei/custom/schema/relaxng/tei_all.rng" type="application/xml" schematypens="http://relaxng.org/ns/structure/1.0"?>
<?xml-model href="http://www.tei-c.org/release/xml/tei/custom/schema/relaxng/tei_all.rng" type="application/xml"
	schematypens="http://purl.oclc.org/dsdl/schematron"?>
<TEI xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <teiHeader>
      <fileDesc>
         <titleStmt>
            <title>My Immortal</title>
         </titleStmt>
         <publicationStmt>
            <p>Originally Published on Fanfiction.net on <date when="2007-03-03">March 3rd,
                  2007</date> It was then removed by Fanfiction.net on <date when="2008-10">October
                     2008</date>for a reason that has never been confirmed. It has since been
               reuploaded onto the site by mutiple people. The upload that we are using was
               published on <date when="2011-03-26">March 26, 2011</date></p>
         </publicationStmt>
     <sourceDesc>
            <p>born digital</p>
         </sourceDesc>
      </fileDesc>
        </teiHeader>
        <text>
           <front>
              <docTitle>
                 <titlePart>Chapter 3 &amp; 4</titlePart>
              </docTitle>
           </front>
      <body>
         <p>On the night of the concert I put on my black lace-up boots with high heels. 
            Underneath them were ripped red fishnets. Then I put on a black leather minidress with all this corset stuff on the back and front. 
            I put on matching fishnet on my arms. I straightened my hair and made it look all spiky. I felt a little depressed then, so I slit one of my wrists. 
            I read a depressing book while I waited for it to stop bleeding and I listened to some GC. I painted my nails black and put on TONS of black eyeliner. 
            Then I put on some black lipstick. I didn't put on foundation because I was pale anyway. I drank some human blood so I was ready to go to the concert.         
         </p>
         <p>I went outside. Draco was waiting there in front of his flying car. He was wearing a Simple Plan t-shirt (they would play at the show too), 
            baggy black skater pants, black nail polish and a little eyeliner (AN: A lot fo kewl boiz wer it ok!).</p>
         <p>"Hi Draco!" I said in a depressed voice.</p>
         <p>"Hi Ebony." he said back. We walked into his flying black Mercedes-Benz (the license plate said 666) and flew to the place with the concert. 
            On the way we listened excitedly to Good Charlotte and Marilyn Manson. We both smoked cigarettes and drugs. 
            When we got there, we both hopped out of the car. We went to the mosh pit at the front of the stage and jumped up and down as we listened to Good Charlotte.</p>
         <lg>
            <l>"You come in cold, you're covered in blood</l>
            <l>They're all so happy you've arrived</l>
            <l>The doctor cuts your cord, hands you to your mom</l>
            <l>She sets you free into this life." sang Joel <note place="parenthes">(I don't own da lyrics 2 <w corresp="that">dat</w> song)</note>.</l>
         </lg>
         <p><said>Joel is so fucking hot</said>. I said to Draco, pointing to him as he sung, filling the club with his amazing voice.</p>
         <p>Suddenly Draco looked sad.</p>
         <p><said>What's wrong?</said> I asked as we moshed to the music. Then I caught on.</p>
         <p><said>Hey, it's ok I don't like him better than YOU!</said> I said.</p>
         <p><said>Really?</said> asked Draco sensitively and he put his arm around me all protective.</p>
         <p><said>>Really.</said>I said. "Besides I don't even know Joel and he's going out with Hilary fucking Duff. I fucking hate that little bitch."
            I said disgustedly, thinking of her ugly blonde face.</p>
         <p>The night went on really well, and I had a great time. So did Draco. After the concert, we drank some beer and asked 
            Benji and Joel for their autographs and photos with them. We got GC concert tees. Draco and I crawled back into the Mercedes-Benz, 
            but Draco didn't go back into Hogwarts, instead he drove the car into… the Forbidden Forest! </p>
      </body>
        </text>
   <text>
      <body>
         <p><note place="start">Chapter 4. AN: I sed stup flaming ok ebony's name is ENOBY nut mary su OK! DRACO IS SOO IN LUV wif her dat he is acting defrent! 
               dey nu eechodder b4 ok!</note></p>
         <p><said>DRACO!</said> I shouted. "What the fuck do you think you are doing?"</p>  
         <p>Draco didn't answer but he stopped the flying car and he walked out of it. I walked out of it too, curiously.</p>
         <p>"What the fucking hell?" I asked angrily.</p>
         <p>Ebony?" he asked.</p>
         <p>"What?" I snapped.</p>
         <p>Draco leaned in extra-close and I looked into his gothic red eyes (he was wearing color contacts) which 
            revealed so much depressing sorrow and evilness and then suddenly I didn't feel mad anymore.</p>
         <p>And then… suddenly just as I Draco kissed me passionately. Draco climbed on top of me and we started to make out keenly against a tree. 
            He took of my top and I took of his clothes. I even took of my bra. Then he put his thingie into my you-know-what and we did it for the first time.</p>
         <p>Oh! Oh! Oh! " I screamed. I was beginning to get an orgasm. We started to kiss everywhere and my pale body became all warm. And then….</p>
         <p>"WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU DOING YOU MOTHERFUKERS!"</p>
         <p> It was….Dumbledore!</p>
      </body>
        </text>
</TEI>
