<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-model href="http://www.tei-c.org/release/xml/tei/custom/schema/relaxng/tei_all.rng" type="application/xml" schematypens="http://relaxng.org/ns/structure/1.0"?>
<?xml-model href="http://www.tei-c.org/release/xml/tei/custom/schema/relaxng/tei_all.rng" type="application/xml"
	schematypens="http://purl.oclc.org/dsdl/schematron"?>
<TEI xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <teiHeader>
      <fileDesc>
         <titleStmt>
            <title>My Immortal</title>
            <author><addName>Tara Gilesbie</addName></author>
         </titleStmt>
         <publicationStmt>
            <p>Originally Published on Fanfiction.net on <date when="2007-03-03">March 3rd,
                  2007</date> It was then removed by Fanfiction.net on <date when="2008-10">October
                  2008</date>for a reason that has never been confirmed. It has since been
               reuploaded onto the site by mutiple people. The upload that we are using was
               published on <date when="2011-03-26">March 26, 2011</date></p>
         </publicationStmt>
         <sourceDesc>
            <p>born digital</p>
         </sourceDesc>
      </fileDesc>
   </teiHeader>
   <text>
      <front>
         <docTitle>
            <titlePart>1. Intro</titlePart>
         </docTitle>
         <head place="top">By: xXMidnightEssenceXx DISCLAIMER: I DID NOT WRITE THIS The infamous
            WORST FANFICTION EVER posted here, unedited, for ur "lulz" -Originally by Tara Gilesbie
            -Rated M for the "Then he put his thingie into my you-know-what and we did it for the
            first time." line! -There is more than 1 chap per page Rated: Fiction M - English -
            Humor/Fantasy - Draco M., OC - Chapters: 14 - Words: 24,152 - Reviews: 7,907 - Favs:
            3,164 - Follows: 1,255 - Updated: Jun 1, 2016 - Published: Mar 16, 2011 - id: 6829556
         </head>
      </front>
      <body>
         <p>Message from xXMidnightEssenceXx: Obviously I did not write this, it was published on
            this site 5 years ago, then removed. There are probably other copies of this on
            FanFiction as well as other sites, but I though I'd post it anyway. Those who remember
            My Immortal well should also remember the first few chapters (1-15) were co-written with
            'Raven' hence they were spelt better etc but don't worry Raven leaves in chapter 16
            (which is where her character Willow gets expelled from Hogwarts). However, she seems to
            return... The copy on here I'm pretty sure is the 100% original version of My Immortal
            with no edits at all outside those by Raven (which were in the original). This version
            will include the 'hacker' chapter 39 and the original chapter 39, and the possibly fake
            "My Immortal 2" if I can find it! I will also include links to the My Immortal "MOVIE"
            and other sites where you can read more at the end. Thank -–or "Fangz"- You!.</p>
         <p>The Return of My Immortal! Excerpt from Encyclopedia Dramatica: My Immortal is the most
            famous, notoriously bad fan fiction ever written. Based very loosely in the Harry Potter
            universe and featuring the blatant Mary-Sue protagonist Ebony (or often times "Enoby")
            Dark'ness Dementia Raven Way, it reads like a detailed list of everything a fanfic
            author could ever possibly do wrong, only taken to exaggerated, horrifying extremes.
            Written by super-tard Tara Gilesbie, My Immortal was originally posted to sometime in
            2006, but was subsequently deleted by the staff after causing a severe drop in the
            site's collective IQ. In fact, the fanfic is so unbelievably bad that many refuse to
            accept that it's real, insisting that Tara was only trolling and that the story is
            really a parody. Regardless of the author's intent, My Immortal remains one of the most
            cringe-worthy, unintentionally hilarious, so-bad-it's-good pieces of literature the
            internets have ever shat out.</p>
         <p>My Immortal unofficial website: http (colon-slash-slash) myimmortalrehost (dot) webs
            (dot) com</p>
      </body>
   </text>
   <text>
      <front>
         <docTitle>
            <titlePart>2. Chapters 1 &amp; 2</titlePart>
         </docTitle>
         <!--for any sort of miss spellings/ slang that Tara does I am trying to mark only ones she uses frequently-->
         <head>Chapters 1 &amp; 2 Chapter 1. AN: Special <w corresp="thanks">fangz</w> (get it, coz
            Im <w corresp="gothic">goffik</w>) <w corresp="to">2</w> my gf (ew not in that way)
            raven, bloodytearz666 <w corresp="for">4</w> helpin me wif <w corresp="the">da</w> story
            and spelling. <w corresp="you">U </w><w corresp="rock">rok!</w> Justin ur da luv of my
            deprzzing life u rok 2! <w corresp="My Chemical Romance">MCR</w>
            ROX!</head>
      </front>
      <body>
         <p>Hi my name is Ebony Dark'ness Dementia Raven Way and I have long ebony black hair (that's how I got my name) with purple streaks and red tips 
            that reaches my mid-back and icy blue eyes like limpid tears and a
            lot of people tell me I look like Amy Lee <note place="parenthesis">(AN: if u don't know who she is get da hell
            out of here!)</note>. I'm not related to Gerard Way but I wish I was because he's a major
            fucking hottie. I'm a vampire but my teeth are straight and white. I have pale white
            skin. I'm also a witch, and I go to a magic school called Hogwarts in England where I'm
            in the seventh year (I'm seventeen). I'm a goth (in case you couldn't tell) and I wear
            mostly black. I love Hot Topic and I buy all my clothes from there. For example today I
            was earing a black corset with matching lace around it and a black leather miniskirt,
            pink fishnets and black combat boots. I was wearing black lipstick, white foundation,
            black eyeliner and red eye shadow. I was walking outside Hogwarts. It was snowing and
            raining so there was no sun, which I was very happy about. A lot of preps stared at me.
            I put up my middle finger at them.</p>
         <p> "Hey Ebony!" shouted a voice. I looked up. It was…. Draco Malfoy!</p>
         <p>"What's up Draco?" I asked. </p>
         <p> "Nothing." he said shyly. But then, I heard my friends call me and I had to go
            away.</p>
         <p>
            <note place="end">AN: IS it good? PLZ tell me fangz!</note></p>
         <p><note type="start">Chapter 2. AN: Fangz 2 bloodytearz666 4 helpin me wif da chapta! BTW
               <w corresp ="non goth">preps</w> stop <w corresp="insulting">flaming</w> ma story ok!</note> The next day I woke
            up in my bedroom. It was snowing and raining again. I opened the door of my coffin and
            drank some blood from a bottle I had. My coffin was black ebony and inside it was hot
            pink velvet with black lace on the ends. I got out of my coffin and took of my giant MCR
            t-shirt which I used for pajamas. Instead, I put on a black leather dress, a pentagram
            necklace, combat boots and black fishnets on. I put on four pairs of earrings in my
            pierced ears, and put my hair in a kind of messy bun. </p>
         <p> My friend, Willow (AN: Raven dis is u!) woke up then and grinned at me. She flipped her long
            waist-length raven black hair with pink streaks and opened her forest-green eyes. She
            put on her Marilyn Manson t-shirt with a black mini, fishnets and pointy high-heeled
            boots. We put on our makeup (black lipstick white foundation and black eyeliner.) </p>
         <p> "OMFG, I saw you talking to Draco Malfoy yesterday!" she
            said excitedly. "Yeah? So?" I said, blushing. "Do you like Draco?" she asked as we went
            out of the Slytherin common room and into the Great Hall. "No I so fucking don't!" I
            shouted. "Yeah right!" she exclaimed. Just then, Draco walked up to me. "Hi." he said.
            "Hi." I replied flirtily. "Guess what." he said. "What?" I asked. "Well, Good Charlotte
            are having a concert in Hogsmeade." he told me. "Oh. My. Fucking. God!" I screamed. I
            love GC. They are my favorite band, besides MCR. "Well…. do you want to go with me?" he
            asked. I gasped. </p>
        
      </body>
   </text>
   <text>
      <front>
         <docTitle>
            <titlePart>3. Chapters 3 &amp; 4</titlePart>
         </docTitle>
         <head>Chapter 3. AN: STOP FLAMMING DA STORY PREPZ OK! odderwize fangs 2 da goffik ppl 4 da good reveiws! FANGS AGEN RAVEN! oh yeah, 
     BTW I don't own dis or da lyrics 4 Good Chralotte.</head></front>
    <body>
       <p>On the night of the concert I put on my black lace-up boots with high heels. 
          Underneath them were ripped red fishnets. Then I put on a black leather minidress with all this corset stuff on the back and front. 
          I put on matching fishnet on my arms. I straightened my hair and made it look all spiky. I felt a little depressed then, so I slit one of my wrists. 
          I read a depressing book while I waited for it to stop bleeding and I listened to some GC. I painted my nails black and put on TONS of black eyeliner. 
          Then I put on some black lipstick. I didn't put on foundation because I was pale anyway. I drank some human blood so I was ready to go to the concert.         
       </p>
       <p>I went outside. Draco was waiting there in front of his flying car. He was wearing a Simple Plan t-shirt (they would play at the show too), 
          baggy black skater pants, black nail polish and a little eyeliner (AN: A lot fo kewl boiz wer it ok!).</p>
       <p>"Hi Draco!" I said in a depressed voice.</p>
       <p>"Hi Ebony." he said back. We walked into his flying black Mercedes-Benz (the license plate said 666) and flew to the place with the concert. 
          On the way we listened excitedly to Good Charlotte and Marilyn Manson. We both smoked cigarettes and drugs. 
          When we got there, we both hopped out of the car. We went to the mosh pit at the front of the stage and jumped up and down as we listened to Good Charlotte.</p>
      <lg>
      <l>"You come in cold, you're covered in blood</l>
         <l>They're all so happy you've arrived</l>
         <l>The doctor cuts your cord, hands you to your mom</l>
         <l>She sets you free into this life." sang Joel <note place="parenthes">(I don't own da lyrics 2 <w corresp="that">dat</w> song)</note>.</l>
      </lg>
       <p>"Joel is so fucking hot." I said to Draco, pointing to him as he sung, filling the club with his amazing voice.</p>
       <p>Suddenly Draco looked sad.</p>
       <p>"What's wrong?" I asked as we moshed to the music. Then I caught on.</p>
       <p>"Hey, it's ok I don't like him better than YOU!" I said.</p>
       <p>"Really?" asked Draco sensitively and he put his arm around me all protective.</p>
       <p>"Really." I said. "Besides I don't even know Joel and he's going out with Hilary fucking Duff. I fucking hate that little bitch."
          I said disgustedly, thinking of her ugly blonde face.</p>
       <p>The night went on really well, and I had a great time. So did Draco. After the concert, we drank some beer and asked 
          Benji and Joel for their autographs and photos with them. We got GC concert tees. Draco and I crawled back into the Mercedes-Benz, 
          but Draco didn't go back into Hogwarts, instead he drove the car into… the Forbidden Forest! </p>
       <p><note place="start">Chapter 4. AN: I sed stup flaming ok ebony's name is ENOBY nut mary su OK! DRACO IS SOO IN LUV wif her dat he is acting defrent! 
             dey nu eechodder b4 ok!</note></p>
       <p>"DRACO!" I shouted. "What the fuck do you think you are doing?"</p>  
       <p>Draco didn't answer but he stopped the flying car and he walked out of it. I walked out of it too, curiously.</p>
           <p>"What the fucking hell?" I asked angrily.</p>
          <p>Ebony?" he asked.</p>
          <p>"What?" I snapped.</p>
       <p>Draco leaned in extra-close and I looked into his gothic red eyes (he was wearing color contacts) which 
          revealed so much depressing sorrow and evilness and then suddenly I didn't feel mad anymore.</p>
       <p>And then… suddenly just as I Draco kissed me passionately. Draco climbed on top of me and we started to make out keenly against a tree. 
          He took of my top and I took of his clothes. I even took of my bra. Then he put his thingie into my you-know-what and we did it for the first time.</p>
       <p>Oh! Oh! Oh! " I screamed. I was beginning to get an orgasm. We started to kiss everywhere and my pale body became all warm. And then….</p>
       <p>"WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU DOING YOU MOTHERFUKERS!"</p>
        <p> It was….Dumbledore!</p>
    </body>
      
   </text>
</TEI>
